{
    "subject": "resource/Survival_of_the_Fittest_(song)",
    "predicate": "property/recorded",
    "object": "1994",
    "human_readable": "The song 'Survival of the Fittest' was recorded in 1994.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8986940383911133,
            "question": "When was the song 'Survival of the Fittest' recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7239201068878174,
            "question": "Is 'Survival of the Fittest' a recent song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856867074966431,
            "question": "What year did the recording of 'Survival of the Fittest' take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6778170466423035,
            "question": "In what decade was 'Survival of the Fittest' recorded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.631359338760376,
            "question": "If someone was born in 1995, would they have been able to hear 'Survival of the Fittest' when it was new?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.523720920085907,
            "question": "How does the recording date of 'Survival of the Fittest' compare to other popular songs from that era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3274380564689636,
            "question": "How old would the recording of 'Survival of the Fittest' be in 2023?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3241429924964905,
            "question": "What types of music were popular around 1994?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2876358926296234,
            "question": "Could someone born in 1980 have heard 'Survival of the Fittest' when it first came out?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23684675991535187,
            "question": "What musical event might have happened around the year 1994?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The song 'Survival of the Fittest' was recorded in 1994.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1883_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could someone born in 1980 have heard 'Survival of the Fittest' when it first came out?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1883_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of music were popular around 1994?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1883_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would the recording of 'Survival of the Fittest' be in 2023?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1883_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1883_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that \"Survival of the Fittest\" was released in 1995, not 1994. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the documents mention that the song \"Survival of the Fittest\" by Mobb Deep was recorded in 1994. In fact, all documents agree that it was released in 1995, and one document even specifies the exact date (May 29, 1995)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that \"Survival of the Fittest\" by Mobb Deep was released on May 29, 1995, from their album The Infamous (1995). There is no mention or support for it being recorded in 1994."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}